<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>我的博客</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 我的博客</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 22:02:51 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>夏日骑行：重拾生活的节奏</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/begin-cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 22:02:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/begin-cycling/</guid>
      <description>今天重新开始了骑行上下班。
毕竟还在七月，北京的太阳正毒，戴上墨镜、手套、围上面巾，穿上防晒服，除了蹬车子伸直腿时露出的脚踝，其他地方都遮的严严实实。
换了一条去公司的路，需要穿过一条河，河上有一座只能两人并排通过的木桥。以前只有晚上下班回家时才会走这条路，河这一段没有路灯，走在桥上，听着流水的声音，别有一番韵味。
因为前段时间换了个小熊的轮胎，没有了原装轮胎的笨重，现在骑行更轻快了许多。
近期越发的感觉终身学习、持续提升自己的重要性，阅读、骑行、健身、摄影、徒步，这些已慢慢发展成了自己的小爱好，而在工作之余独立完成一些项目，也是自己希望能一直坚持下去的事。
强健体魄，丰富精神，提升生存技巧，就先从骑行开始吧！
骑行刚开始时追求速度，但现在只想慢慢的骑，能一直骑下去。
 下班途中最喜欢的一段路
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warsaw, Poland</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/warsaw-poland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/warsaw-poland/</guid>
      <description>Palace of Culture and Science (Polish: Pałac Kultury i Nauki), is a notable high-rise building in central Warsaw, Poland. With a total height of 237 metres (778 ft) it is the tallest building in Poland, the 5th-tallest building in the European Union (including spire) and one of the tallest on the European continent. Constructed in 1955, it houses various public and cultural institutions such as cinemas, theatres, libraries, sports clubs, university faculties and authorities of the Polish Academy of Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hel, Poland</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/hel-poland-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/hel-poland-3/</guid>
      <description>Hel Peninsula (Polish: Mierzeja Helska) is a 35-km-long sand bar peninsula in northern Poland separating the Bay of Puck from the open Baltic Sea. The width of the peninsula varies from approximately 300 m near Jurata, through 100 m in the most narrow part to over 3 km at the tip. Since the peninsula was formed entirely of sand, it is frequently turned into an island by winter storms. Until the 17th century the peninsula was a chain of islands that formed a strip of land only during the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hel, Poland</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/hel-poland-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/hel-poland-2/</guid>
      <description>Hel Peninsula (Polish: Mierzeja Helska) is a 35-km-long sand bar peninsula in northern Poland separating the Bay of Puck from the open Baltic Sea. The width of the peninsula varies from approximately 300 m near Jurata, through 100 m in the most narrow part to over 3 km at the tip. Since the peninsula was formed entirely of sand, it is frequently turned into an island by winter storms. Until the 17th century the peninsula was a chain of islands that formed a strip of land only during the summer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona, US</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/arizona-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/arizona-us/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Canyon is a steep-sided canyon carved by the Colorado River in Arizona, United States. The canyon is 277 miles (446 km) long, up to 18 miles (29 km) wide and attains a depth of over a mile (6,093 feet or 1,857 meters).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago, US</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/chicago-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/chicago-us/</guid>
      <description>Chicago, officially the City of Chicago, is the most populous city in the U.S. state of Illinois, and the third-most-populous city in the United States. With an estimated population of 2,705,994 (2018), it is also the most populous city in the Midwestern United States. Chicago is the county seat of Cook County, the second-most-populous county in the US, with a small portion of the northwest side of the city extending into DuPage County near O&amp;rsquo;Hare Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panaji, India</title>
      <link>https://example.com/photos/panaji-india-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/photos/panaji-india-2/</guid>
      <description>Panaji, formerly Panjim, is the capital of the Indian state of Goa and the headquarters of North Goa district. It lies on the banks of the Mandovi River estuary in the Ilhas de Goa sub-district (taluka). With a population of 114,759 in the metropolitan area, Panjim is Goa&amp;rsquo;s largest urban agglomeration, ahead of Margão and Vasco da Gama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>A minimal, responsive and light theme for Hugo inspired by Linux console.
Installation $ mkdir themes $ cd themes $ git submodule add https://github.com/mrmierzejewski/hugo-theme-console.git hugo-theme-console See the Hugo documentation for more information.
Configuration Set theme parameter in your config file:
theme = &amp;quot;hugo-theme-console&amp;quot; License Copyright © 2024 Marcin Mierzejewski
The theme is released under the MIT License. Check the original theme license for additional licensing information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
